export const decks = {
  Literature: {
    title: "Literature",
    cards: [
      {
        question: "In Pride and Prejudice, who does Jane Bennet marry?",
        answer: "Charles Bingley",
      },
      {
        question: "Which country is Aesop’s Fables believed to originate from?",
        answer: "Greece",
      },
      {
        question: `In Franz Kafka's "The Metamorphosis" what is Gregor Samsa transformed into?`,
        answer: "An insect",
      },
      {
        question: `What is the novel "Frankenstein’s" alternative name?`,
        answer: "The Modern Prometheus",
      },
    ],
  },
  Biology: {
    title: "Biology",
    cards: [
      {
        question:
          "What’s the first thing a caterpillar usually eats after it’s born?",
        answer: `It's own eggshell`,
      },
      {
        question: "Name a plant that forms seeds but not fruits",
        answer: "Banana",
      },
      {
        question: "An ant warns other ants of danger ahead by doing what?",
        answer: "Sending chemical signals",
      },
    ],
  },
  Mathematics: {
    title: "Mathematics",
    cards: [
      {
        question: "What is 8% of $600?",
        answer: `$48`,
      },
      {
        question: "What is 35% expressed as a decimal?",
        answer: "0.35",
      },
      {
        question: "What is the sum of two complementary angles, in degrees?",
        answer: "90",
      },
      {
        question: "What is an integer?",
        answer: "A whole number.",
      },
    ],
  },
};
